Narrator:
Stewie Griffin--
scientist, inventor, infant.
Searching for a way to tap
into the hidden strengths
That all humans have.
Then an accidental overdose
Of gamma radiation
alters his body chemistry.
(thunder rumbles)
And now whenever stewie griffin
grows angry or outraged,
A startling metamorphosis occurs.
Oh, I hurt myself changing a tire!
(thunder rumbles)
NARRATOR:
The creature is driven by rage
and pursued by
an investigative reporter.
Mr. Tucker, don't
make me angry.
You wouldn't like
me when I'm angry.
NARRATOR:
The creature is wanted for
a murder he didn't commit.
Stewie Griffin
is believed to be dead.
And he must let the world
think that he is dead,
until he can find a way
to control
the raging spirit
that dwells within him.
(roars)
Oh, come on, can we please
change the channel?
I can't stand
local news.
No, Brian.
The new female anchor
is about to do that
Child of the Month segment.
I like her.
Good evening,
I'm Joyce Kinney.
And this is April's
Child of the Month,
eight-year-old Angus Reed.
Angus was born
with cerebral palsy.
And his only wish is to one day
become a famous heart surgeon.
All I want to do is help people.
Child of the Month, Angus Reed.
Good luck with
your dream, Angus.
We believe in you.
What a weird little guy.
Thanks, Joyce.
How old do they usually
live to be, by the way?
Well, you never see
a gray-haired one.
Ah, so inspiring.
(church bells ringing)
Mom, there's a row
open up there.
Oh, good, I like
sitting in the front.
Me, too.
I didn't dress up
not to be seen.
Hey, you, go easy on
the communion wine today.
Don't want another one
of your drunken mishaps.
(baby talk):
Let me get at that belly.
Let me kiss that belly.
(laughing)
Stop it!
Cut it out!
I'm gonna give you
a flubber kiss.
Oh, Lois,
that tickles!
Flubber-belly,
pork-belly Stewie.
(blows raspberries)
(both laughing)
Ah, give me that belly!
(blows raspberries)
(groaning)
(coughing)
(screaming)
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
(chuckles)
I got a little nervous.
It's just,
I like you so much.
Please turn to hymn number 487.
(organ playing hymn)
♪ If we praise Jesus
by singing all together ♪
♪ It makes this whole exercise
seem less bizarre ♪
♪ Than it really is
when you actually stand back ♪
♪ And examine it
with some objectivity ♪
♪ Amen. ♪
PRIEST:
Please be seated.
Let me remind you all that
this Saturday at 5:00 p.m.,
we'll have vespers,
not to be confused
with the Italian motor scooter.
(polite laughter,
Lois laughing loudly)
(Lois continues laughing)
LOIS:
Vespers!
And don't forget, next weekend,
we will have the Sunday
afternoon family picnic--
as God said to Noah--
weather permitting.
(polite laughter,
Lois laughing loudly)
(Lois continues laughing)
Stop it!
And another reminder:
When you arrive to mass,
please do not park
behind the rectory.
As the Corinthians said to
the Galatians, "That's my land."
(polite laughter,
Lois laughing loudly)
Oh, ho, ho!
Look out, Gallagher!
PETER:
Stop kissing ass.
Bless you.
Have a wonderful day.
Thank you, Father.
Hey, nice talk, chief.
There you go.
Buy the wife something pretty.
Oh, Father, your homily
was so moving today.
Thank you, Lois.
And thank you for
the great job you did
with the rummage sale for
the needy last weekend.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
You know, I accidentally almost
put a cashmere sweater in there.
Can you believe?
(chuckles)
What would one of them do
with a cashmere sweater?
You know, Lois, we also
have a bake sale coming up,
and we're short
about eight pies.
Well, I'll hit the grocery store
this afternoon
and get to work.
PETER:
Okay, Lois, bye!
Bye, church!
Bye, church guy!
Bye, unending conversation!
Bye, terrible church people!
Bye!
My God, does everything have
to have a mascot these days?
I mean, look, there's a lion in
overalls on the aluminum foil.
I mean, wh-who
is that for?
No, Lois, don't
get that one!
Get the one with the
lion in overalls!
(gasps)
Oh, my God, look!
It's Joyce Kinney
from Channel Five.
Excuse me, Miss Kinney?
I don't mean to bother you,
but my name is Lois Griffin.
I-I am a huge fan,
and I just think
you are doing
a fantastic job.
And after what I went through
with Diane Simmons,
well, let me
just say it's nice
to be standing here
with no one trying to murder me.
Yeah, no, you're fine.
Oh, well, that's very
nice of you to say.
You know, it's my
first anchoring job,
and I'm trying to make
a good impression.
I love the "Child
of the Month" segment.
We just watched that one
with the little goofball
who thought he was
going to be a doctor.
Ah, I can't believe
I'm actually meeting you.
You know, the news is so much
better with you on it.
Well, you know, Lois,
I'm on my way back to
the station after lunch.
I'd be happy to
give you a tour.
Oh, my goodness.
That'd be wonderful.
Great. Why don't
you come down
to the station
around 6:00?
You can watch
the broadcast.
Okay. I'll see you then.
Oh, wait-wait.
BILF.
Total BILF.
Yeah, so, going pretty good.
I got six pacifiers now.
That was a big nothing.
And Julie Andrews
pleaded not guilty,
saying that she
brought the gun
to the nightclub
for protection.
And that's all for today's
Channel Five News at 6:00.
Oh, I almost forgot.
That little girl
is still missing.
Do we have a picture?
Do we... We-we don't?
We don't have a picture?
Okay, we don't have
a picture. Okay.
But she's...
She's Puerto Rican.
So look out
for a Puerto Rican.
(news theme playing)
We're clear.
That was so much
fun to watch.
What a pro you are.
Lois,
you've met Tom Tucker.
Oh, yes, of course.
I loved that
piece you did
on the invention
of the guillotine.
Oh, thank you.
You know,
half the time those things
didn't really work.
How was it, honey?
Ah, they couldn't finish.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I got
to go back tomorrow.
Oh, well, I made
cabbage for dinner.
Yeah, that would be
the ending to this day.
In here is our editor, Mike.
They let him smoke inside
because all the smoke
from his cigarette
just floats directly back up
into his face.
(hoarsely): Hey, Joyce,
when you get a chance,
come take a look
at the Weekapaug thing.
Oh, this is all
so fascinating.
You must have
so many stories.
Well, look, if you want to grab
a drink with me later tonight,
I'd be happy to
tell you some.
Oh, my God,
I would love to.
Look at me, huh?
Stepping out on the town
with a big celebrity.
Well, I think
you're exaggerating.
No, you're a lady big shot,
like Miss Piggy.
Hey, Kermit.
What happened to the
"Bears in Space" sketch?
Sorry, it's
"Pigs in Space" now.
There's been a change.
What?
There's been a change!
TV ANNOUNCER:
We now return to
Ellen Only Talks
When Her Guest Is Talking.
So, you want to
hear about my movie?
I had a great weekend.
We spent three
months shooting
in Louisiana.
I danced all over my house.
And, you know, it's a thriller.
It's really a love story, too.
I try to dance in every room
at least once a week. I also
listen to jazz while I vacuum,
which is cool.
Anyway, it comes out
Friday. I got to work
with Julianna Marguiles.
My pets were going wild
all weekend. I think there's,
like, something in the air.
Could not have been nicer.
Like smog or pollen.
Or pollinated smog, or...
Are you just gonna talk
over everything that I say?
I love talking on TV.
I'll-I'll do anything
to talk on TV.
Hiya, lame asses.
(all shouting in protest)
Whoa. We were having
a nice time.
Sorry. I'm just
painfully aware
that I'm the only
member of this family
who's going out for drinks
with a celebrity tonight.
What are you talking about?
Joyce Kinney invited
me out for drinks.
(laughs)
So just order a pizza
or something, okay?
See you guys later.
Man, I hate calling
that pizza place.
They don't speak English, and
they always mess up the order.
It's like trying to give my cell
phone number to the housekeeper.
Okay, I'm expecting a very
important delivery at the house.
So, could you please
call me if it arrives?
I'll give you
my cell number.
Okay. Yes.
No problem.
Give me number.
Okay. 401-555-1125.
Four...
(sighs)
Four, zero...
Four, four, zero...
No, no, I was just
repeating the four.
One four.
One, four...
All right,
let's start over.
Four, zero, one.
Four.
Zero.
Zero...
One.
Four, zero, one.
Yes.
Five, five, five.
Five. Five. Five.
That was painless.
Okay.
One, one, two, five.
One one, two five.
There you go, you got it.
One, five, five.
What?
You say, "One one,
two fives."
One, five, five.
No, no. Not one one
and two fives.
Two ones.
Two, one, one,
one, two, five.
Oh, my God.
Okay. How many ones?
I'm not giving you
quantities of the numbers,
I'm giving you the numbers.
One, one, two, five.
Those are the
last four numbers.
Okay, one...
One, one.
Two.
Five.
Five. Oh, I see.
One, one, two, five.
Yes! One, one, two, five.
All right, now,
read the number back to me.
L-Let me get my pen.
And that's why whenever
I have sex without protection,
I call it, "taking
a John Chancellor."
(both laughing)
Oh, my God, Joyce, you've
got so many great stories.
Oh, come on,
I'm sure
you've done some
crazy stuff in your time.
Well...
Oh, what is it?
No, n-n-no, I can't.
Lois, I feel like we're
really bonding here tonight.
Come on, let's hear it.
Well, I have had an abortion.
(snoring)
Oh, wake me up
when you got something good.
Oh, my goodness,
sarcastic sleeping.
That puts a lot
of pressure on me.
All right, well,
when I was in college,
I was in an adult film.
Oh, my God,
you did a porno?
Shh! Please, please, please
do not say a word to anybody.
I have never told anyone
that, not even my husband.
I promise,
I'll take it to the grave,
But oh, my God, Lois,
that's hilarious!
Do you have a copy?
Oh, no, that movie's
long gone.
Like the original
ending to Grease.
♪ ...together ♪
♪ Rama-lama, ding-dong ♪
♪ We'll always be together ♪
♪ De pom, de pom, de pom,
de pom ♪
♪ Rama-lama ding-dong... ♪
(wind whistling)
We've been up here
for four days.
Why did you drive
the car into the air
if you didn't know how
to get it back down?
Look, Sandy, it seemed like
a good idea at the time.
Obviously,
I didn't think ahead.
It's so cold.
Let's cuddle together
for warmth.
I-I'm... I'm, I'm,
I'm warm enough.
Quick, we gotta
turn the channel.
I promised my friend Joyce
I'd watch the news tonight.
♪ Channel Five ♪
♪ We're there for you ♪
♪ When times are tough ♪
♪ We'll help you through ♪
♪ With news and sports
and weather ♪
♪ We'll always be together ♪
♪ We're with you
through it all ♪
♪ Channel Five. ♪
Holy (beep), that just
turned out awful.
Joyce, do your thing.
Thanks, Tom.
Pornography.
The very word conjures up
images of red-light districts,
unprotected sex, and of course,
the turn-of-the-century
pornograph machine.
(gears clicking)
Whoa-ho-ho! Sweet Mary!
But it seems pornography
has finally found its way
to our neighborhood.
Yes, local housewife and
church organist Lois Griffin
has revealed to this reporter
that she appeared
in a pornographic movie
back in the early 1980s.
What?!
Mom, that's you!
(laughs)
Boy, that black bar would be
a lot lower now, huh? Huh?
Huh? Would it not?
Evidently, Lois Griffin,
star citizen of Quahog,
is also Lois Griffin,
star of "Quest for Fur."
It just goes to show
you never know
what sort of person
is living next door.
Tom?
I can't
believe this!
Lois, you were in a porno?
She totally betrayed me!
I thought girlfriends were
supposed to support each other.
Ha! Slut!
How could you do
that to me, Joyce?!
Oh. Hello, Lois.
I told you that in confidence!
You totally humiliated me!
Well, then I guess
now we're even.
What?!
What are you talking about?
I never did anything to you!
You really don't
remember me, do you?
Remember you?
We went to high
school together, Lois?
Chemistry class?
Freshman year?
Joycie?
You're Joyce
Chevapravatdumrong?
Yes, but they'd never
let that name on TV,
so I changed it to Kinney.
You ruined my adolescence, Lois.
You told me
I'd made the cheer squad,
blindfolded me, and told me
we were going for a special
celebration breakfast.
When you took
the blindfold off,
I was standing
in front of the entire school
with my pants around my ankles
and a hot dog in my mouth.
(laughter)
It was a horrible
thing to do, Lois.
Look, Joyce,
that was a long time ago.
And I'm very sorry
for what I did.
But we're adults now,
and that doesn't
give you any reason
to humiliate me like this.
Boo-hoo.
You don't like it,
you can go talk to a reporter.
Oh, my God.
I thought we
were friends.
The kind of really good friends
that communicate with each other
poorly through Facebook.
Everyone, I think
it's important
that we talk openly
about this.
It was back in a disgusting
period known as the early '80s.
It was a time
when women would stand topless,
high on coke,
on the edge of hotel balconies
while the curtains
were billowing around them.
I think there was actually
more wind back then.
♪ ♪
MAN:
Hey, Lois, get back inside!
This coke isn't
gonna snort itself!
Great party, Raoul.
I feel like I'm horkin'
all your cocaine.
Hey, that's okay, Lois.
You can just buy
the next bag, eh?
Right, other guy?
♪ ♪
Oh, I couldn't
afford that.
My daddy's making me pay for
my own tuition this semester
because I maxed out
all my credit cards
buying a copy of E.T.
at the video store.
It was $399.
Yeah, but you own it.
You can just
watch that now.
And besides, I got another way
you can make money.
So Raoul gave me a job
at his pet store,
but I still
needed money.
One day
I was cleaning a bird cage,
and a porn producer came in,
and... well, the rest you know.
I kind of feel like, the part
that we should have seen was...
You know what?
Never mind. It works.
Good Lord.
Am I a porn baby?
No. Stewie, come on.
I-I doubt it.
I mean, maybe, yeah.
Probably, yes.
(crowd chatter)
Your mom's in a porno!
I saw her boobs!
Shut up!
Hey, Griffin,
your mom's a whore!
Come on, guys,
knock it off!
Yeah, Griffin, your
mom's gross and nasty!
Hey!
Not cool!
That's
a dude's mom!
Well... she's
also my mom.
Aw, your mom's
a whore!
Yeah! Suck it!
You're a
whore-daughter!
Yeah, Griffin
gets it!
(bell tolling)
Boy, I'm really
looking forward to this.
I really need some church
after the week I've had.
(crowd murmuring)
(coughs)
Sinner.
Harlot.
(coughs)
Skank.
(coughing)
I'm actually sick.
You are no longer
welcome here, Lois Griffin.
But, Father, I've been an active
member of this church for...
Leave this house of God!
(crowd chattering)
But-but I love the church.
It's an important part
of my life.
Maybe you should've thought
of that before you made a porn.
But, Father,
I didn't mean...
Wait. Did you
say "a porn?"
Yes.
Oh.
Well, that's kind of weird.
Why?
Well, I mean,
you'd either say,
"You made porn,"
or "You made a porno."
Y-You don't say,
"Made a porn."
It just...
It hits the ear wrong.
Oh, God, have I been saying
it wrong this whole time?
(crying)
Come on, Lois.
If it makes you feel
any better, I don't care.
And what does it matter what
those people in church think?
I mean, most of of them are
just random background people
we've never seen
before anyway.
Half of them
don't even move;
the other
half just blink.
Peter, that-that's
very sweet,
but how am I supposed
to live in this town
if I'm a social pariah?
What's that?
Is that them little
fish that eat cows?
Just-just
leave me alone, please.
(sighs)
Hey, Lois, can I talk
to you for a second?
For the last time, Brian,
there's no link to it
anywhere online.
No, no, that-that's not...
that's not what I'm here for.
Look, Lois, you
did what you did,
and there's nothing you
can change about that.
But those people can only
make you feel ashamed
if you let them.
If you own the
choice that you made,
you-you take away
all their power
to make you feel
bad about yourself.
What do you mean?
Well, you remember
a few years back,
people used to
make all those jokes
about how Ryan
Seacrest was gay?
And then he started making
those jokes himself,
and now nobody makes
those jokes anymore.
I mean, he's still gay,
but now it's no fun
to joke about it,
because he-he beat
us to the punch.
My God!
That little pole-smoker's
a (bleep) genius!
...and so did the Corinthians
finally write back
to Saint Paul, saying,
"Dude, enough with the letters.
"We have received them all,
"and will get back to you
when we have the time.
"And by the way,
"a lot of the information
you're asking for
is available online."
Oh, look, everybody,
it's the burning bush.
(crowd murmuring)
Hello, Father.
I thought I made it clear that
you are no longer welcome here.
You know, I've been coming
to this church for years.
I've heard all the stories.
Who did Jesus hang around with?
Mary Magdalene.
And who was she?
A prostitute.
Which means,
if they had cameras back then,
I bet she would have done
a porno.
(crowd murmuring)
(whirring)
And if she did,
I know that Jesus
would have forgiven her.
Am I any worse
than Mary Magdalene?
And more importantly,
are you all better than Jesus?
I'm better
than Jesus.
Okay, yes, Tina Fey,
you're better than Jesus.
But the rest of you...
The rest of you need
to accept the fact
that I made a simple mistake.
And here it is.
(projector clicking,
music playing)
(all gasping)
I know I'm a man of God...
but that (bleep) is hot!
(applause, cheering
and whooping)
Oh, look at that.
See, now I'm really starting
to get suspicious.
Somebody order a pizza?
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru